where does
discipline come
from it's pretty
simple and pretty
obvious discipline comes from
within it's an internal
Force now sure of course you can have
discipline posed On You
by some person like like a drill
instructor or like
that self-help Guru on TV but the
reality is that type of discipline isn't
the real type of discipline that we're
talking about that discipline isn't as
strong it won't
survive what you
need is
self-discipline now self-discipline
comes from the self it comes from
you it comes from when you make a
decision to be
disciplined when you make a decision to
be better when you make a decision to do
more and to be
more self-discipline comes when you
decide that you're going to make a mark
on the world and if you
think that you're not disciplined or you
can't be disciplined it's because you
you haven't yet decided to be
disciplined it's because you haven't
created that
discipline
yet so make the decision make the
commitment discipline the root quality
that will improve every aspect of your
life and it'll make you better and
stronger and smarter and faster and
healthier and most
[Music]
[Applause]
importantly it'll make you
free